Hello, everyone. Can you hear us?
Hello, everyone.
Today, we are going to do a new 6.1 live stream.
Today, we are going to talk about these 10 modules.
I will talk about the first 5 modules.
I will talk about the last 5 modules.
You can start your notes with your notebooks.
Let's start today's live stream.
If you have any questions, you can ask them in the chat.
Let's get started.
This 6.1 live stream is mainly about 10 modules.
I will explain each module one by one.
The first one is about the new features.
You can see that this is our list today.
Let's take a look at each module one by one.
First of all, you can see that this is our 6.1 software page.
You can see that we have made a small change in the page.
The tool bar was defaulted at the top and then changed to the left side.
This is an adjustment to the tool bar.
The tools are more and more in the back.
If you put it on the left side, you can see all the tools.
You can connect to our website, Closet Connect, in the software.
You can see the products that are on sale or have already been purchased.
Next is the link for the connection.
This website of Closet Connect is made by the original Closet Lab and MaxPlace.
It is a open resource sharing and communication platform.
You can upload or download some items from it, such as clothes and fabric.
Or some accessories.
Some of the files here are free and you can download some of them.
Let's take a look at some of the contents of our website.
In addition to this, we have also added a new model in our library, Amta.
First, let's take a look at the resources we have added for female models.
In addition to female models, we have also added a male model, which is a black model.
Next, let's take a look at another new feature called Editor 3D.
This feature allows us to directly edit the editor at the 3D window, and it can also be connected to the 2D version.
Let's take a look at some of the tools here.
There are three tools in total.
Let's take a look at the first one, which is the editor shape line tool.
First of all, we select the version that needs to be edited, and then it will speed up.
Then we click on the point to drag the point of this version, and then we will move along with each other.
Then, if you move the line, you can change the frequency of this line.
All these changes can be seen in the 2D window.
The second tool is called the zoom shape line.
If you select the version that needs to be edited, then you can zoom in on this shape line.
This is to increase the frequency.
You can also zoom in on a certain point.
Let's take a look at the last tool, which is called the 3D shape line.
You can also click on the shape line on the 3D version.
Then, if you directly double click on the version,
what we will see here is a straight line.
If you left-click on the version,
then what you create here is a curve.
And our version will be edited along with our shape line.
If you have any questions about the new features,
you can post them in the comments.
I will also explain them to you at any time.
This is one of the functions of our edit shape.
Next is a function called the selection grid.
We can use the selection grid tool.
Let's take a look.
First of all, in the upper right corner of its page,
we can make some adjustments to the brush's strength,
focal length, and size.
We can adjust it to a suitable size.
After the adjustment is done,
we can select the grid in the 3D window.
We can separate it.
Here, I can switch to the grid surface.
Let's take a look.
We can see that this is the grid.
The grid in the 3D window is thinner than the grid in other places.
Here, we can separate the grid in the horizontal grid.
In addition to selecting the grid in the 3D window,
we can also select the grid in the 2D version.
We can select it and make it a part of the fixed frame.
We can also choose to make it a horizontal freeze.
We can adjust the motion of the grid in the 3D window.
Here, we can go back to the 3D window.
Let's go back and check the 3D image.
We can see that the grid in the 3D window is frozen.
We have to make sure that the grid doesn't move when we are editing.
And finally, we can select the fold portion to be moved.
Let's have a look.
You can also change the shape of the foldable part of the model.
This way, the foldable details will not be changed when we simulate the model.
The next feature is the function that allows us to customize the parts of the virtual model.
This function is called the face of the virtual model.
Let's see how to edit the face of the virtual model.
First, we need to select the virtual model.
Click on Edit.
Here you can see the face of the virtual model.
You can see that the virtual model is still in English.
We will translate it later in the video.
Don't worry.
Let's continue.
Here we can find the body model.
The bottom one is the skin model.
Here you can select the skin model of the virtual model.
There is a model button next to it.
You can choose the color of the hair and skin.
You can choose the color in the color card.
On the right side, you can see the different mixing modes.
You can choose a suitable mixing mode.
You can choose the color of the skin.
You can see that the effects of different mixing modes are different.
You can also change the color of the hair and skin.
You can also change the shape of the eyebrows.
Yes, it's Alphandau.
Blue Alphandau.
You can also change the color of the eyebrows.
You can also change the shape of the lips.
You can also change the color of the lip.
Blue.
And let's have a look at this.
You can change the color of did foundation to change something.
Coming to the next process is the UV editor.
Here is where the cover version will be pimples.
Repeat this process multiple times.
We can use the same sticker to make a texture for it.
First, let's see how to make the same sticker.
Let's go to the UI editor mode first,
and then click on the backup texture.
Then choose a save path for it.
Here, we can save it as a normal PNG or JPG format.
Now we have added a pdf format for it.
Let's click on the save button again.
In the bottom, we can save it simultaneously,
such as text, metal, hair, light and transparency.
We can also choose the desired save picture and then click on the save button.
Here we can save a.
If it is a non-magnificent costume, but it also contains cherry blossoms, we can use a unified sticker for it.
We can choose this material and change its Texture Map to Unified in the editor.
Then we can import a UV map of the texture we just saved.
That's it.
We can also adjust the text of this version in the UV editor.
Some people say the sound is too quiet.
Let me turn up the volume a little bit.
Finally, we can add a new function called GRTF Unified.
Here we can import the physical properties and text of the texture into a GRTF format.
We can import FabricGRTF into the format.
Here we can import the text of the texture into a GRTF format.
Then we click Save.
As you can see, there are only three objects in total.
But in the object window, there are four fabrics in total.
This is because the fabric at the top is a Substance fabric.
Due to the problem of license, we can't export Substance fabric.
We can only export a fabric for our system's automatic production.
Here we can choose the fabric you need to export and its file type.
After choosing, click OK.
Then we can export all the fabrics to it.
Now we can import all the fabrics to it.
We can import the GRTF2.0.
We can find the file that we just saved.
Here we can change this object from a virtual model to an object.
Here we can see the three fabrics we have imported.
If you don't necessarily need these three types of materials,
you can choose these three.
It will be imported directly,
and then you can apply it to it separately.
This is our GRTF.
We just talked about the main new features of our 6.1
update and optimization.
Now let's take a look at the file.
As you can see, our update is very optimized.
This is the point we need to talk about later.
The first update is that you can save the 3D clothing record
in the GPRG file.
First, let's see where to save the 3D clothing record.
We open the history record,
and then there is a 3D clothing record in the upper right corner.
If you click here, you can record a 3D clothing.
Then we will make some modifications to this clothing later.
When we make any modifications to it later,
we can click on the record 3D clothing again
to get a new 3D clothing.
Here we can see that the 3D clothing record
in the GPRG file is the same as before.
After we're done here, we're going to record the 3D costume again.
And then we're going to give this model a different pose.
Sorry, there's a little bit of a problem with our internet today.
And then we're going to record the 3D costume.
We can see that this is the 3D costume we just recorded.
When we double-click it, it will be directly switched to the costume record.
Now we can save this file.
When we save it, the 3D costume records we just saved will also be saved along with the GPRG file.
Now we can open the file we just saved and take a look at it.
You can see that the 3D costume records we just saved are still in the historical record.
This way, it's easier for us to compare and confirm the design during the design process.
The second new feature is that we can set the center axis for rotating the video.
Let's take a look at this new feature.
When we rotate the video, it's still in the costume.
Now we've added three new options here.
Let's take a look at them one by one.
The first option is called Automatic.
When we select Automatic, it will rotate the video to the center of the 3D window with the costume and virtual model.
You can see that the center is in the middle of Alice and the dog.
If we change it to the center of the 3D logo,
it will rotate the video to the center with the X and Z axis of the 3D window.
The last option is Automatic.
In Automatic, we can enter the X and Z axis of the 3D model and take a look at the 3D model.
It will rotate the video until the camera is in the center of it.
You can see that the 3D model is in the center of the 3D model and the X is in the center of it.
After that, we click on Start Recording.
In our costume video here, we have a new optimization.
Our video is now supported in mp4 format.
We have the original avi support avi format, and now we have a new mp4 format.
You can save the saved video to mp4 format.
The next update is a small update at the 3D window.
It's called 3D Fast Frame, display or hide grid.
First, let's take a look at how to save a fast frame.
When saving a fast frame, we can open the grid at the 3D window.
This way, it's easy for us to create a layout for it during the fast frame process.
Next, we have another function called Distribute JRTF.
In this function, we can display the colors and the costumes of the animation.
Let's take a look.
For a costume like this, it has a color.
There are two color files here.
And then there's an animation of a walk.
Here we have the color and the walk animation.
Let's make a draft of it.
I'm going to choose the draft here.
And then we'll choose JRTF 2.0.
When we draft it, we're going to enter our username and password here.
You can see that we've added two options to its window.
We've added two options to its window.
One is called Save Color in the file.
The other one is called Save Costume Animation in the object window.
These two options.
Then we click OK.
In this JRTF file that we've drafted,
it contains color and costume animation.
Next, we're going to go to an application called Substance.
Previously, we could directly apply the Substance fabric to our fabric.
Now we can also apply it to the virtual model.
All you have to do is select this virtual model.
Then change its material from PBR material to Substance material.
Then select a material and put it in the corresponding window.
Look at this little dog.
This is the Substance fabric.
In addition to being applied to virtual models,
it can also be applied to buttons.
Let's take a look at how to apply it to buttons.
Select this button to change its properties
from PBR properties to Substance properties.
This also gives it a Substance property.
This is a Substance property applied to buttons.
In addition to that, it can also be applied to add-ons.
The same applies to PBR properties as well.
Just like this.
The next update in the file is that
we can set the layout of the
In the past, when we saved 3D clothing,
when we saved the PBRD file,
the layout of the sketch was saved
with the layout of the 3D window.
Now we can set it.
In the settings, we can find the user profile.
In the user profile,
we can find a project default file here.
Then we can find its project.
This is called the solid layout.
We can change it to the solid layout.
This off opens it.
First of all, here,
we can change it to a default private view,
which is a private view of the policy table.
You can take a look.
Let me show you this.
Let me show you what the private view looks like.
Here, we want to see
the private view we saved.
It automatically adapts to the entire clothing,
instead of adapting to all the objects.
In addition to the private view,
there is also an MVS format.
It is a quick view view.
If you have saved this complete quick view,
you can open it directly and use it.
Let's take a look at this view.
This is the solid layout saved
with the quick view view.
Next, we will take a look at the optimization in the DXF file.
In the DXF window,
we have added two options.
The first one is called remove non-plot points.
If you choose this option when you import,
it will delete the number of points
that do not have the number of points
in the DXF file.
Let's have a look at the question.
There is also an option called
convert the non-plot points.
If you choose this option,
you can convert the non-plot points
in the DXF file
to the non-plot points that
Glove can detect.
Then let's hook up the two of them, click on the checkbox, and import this file into it.
Here you can see the address, you can see that the address line here is what we can identify in our software.
You can use the tool to select the address line and adjust the size of it.
The next update in DXF is that you can import IUL files.
When we have a password, but we can't successfully import it,
you can just click here to open an IUL file.
After clicking,
you can open this IUL file and it will contain this password.
Let's take a look at some of the improvements in 3D.
Let's take a look.
The first improvement is that we have added a feature called 3D Basics Pen.
Let's choose to use this 3D Basics Pen.
This tool.
We can use this 3D Basics Pen tool to draw a basic line on a 3D window or 2D version.
Let's draw it first.
After drawing, we can actually adjust this basic line through the edit version tool.
Before we adjust it, we first need to unlock the basic line and adjust it.
After adjusting it, we can just put the inner line of the pocket into the basic line.
Then, we can rearrange the 3D window version.
Let's go to the 3D window version.
This is an advantage of folding arrangement.
Now, when the 3D version is a symmetrical version,
when we use the folding arrangement,
we only need to fold one side,
and the other side will also automatically be folded.
We can see, we don't need to fold it twice again.
I can adjust the angle of the fold.
Next, we are going to update the shape line.
We can edit the pattern in the pattern rendering.
This is the position of the inner line or the outer line of the pattern.
For example, the bottom of the T-shirt is a circle.
But in the pattern rendering, because it is in the pattern rendering,
it is not in the pattern rendering.
So it is not in the pattern rendering.
But in the pattern rendering, because it is wearing pants,
the bottom line is not displayed.
You can select the bottom line and adjust the position of the Z-axis.
Now we can see the Z-axis of the bottom of the T-shirt in the pattern rendering.
You can take a look.
In addition to adjusting the pattern line,
we can also adjust the inner line of the Z-axis.
For example, we hide the line of the T-shirt.
After hiding it, the inner line of the pocket is not very clear.
You can select this inner line and enlarge the Z-axis of the T-shirt.
This way, the inner line can be clearly seen in the pattern rendering.
This is what we just did.
This is the optimization of the 3D window.
Let's take a look at it.
This is the optimization of some of the functions in the 3D window.
Now let's take a look at some of the optimization in the 2D function.
First of all, the first optimization is that we have added a new function,
which is a version of the finished pattern.
This is a function of the finished pattern.
It is just like typing in a blank space,
it has a pop up dialog box.
You can create a pattern for it directly.
The first is a radius of the inner side of the center distance.
We can input its inner length,
and its outer length,
including its inside and outside width,
and its inner side,
and its inner side width.
This is a radius from the inside to the outside.
And its direction.
It's done.
Now we can sew it on.
This is a dragon board.
Now we can change it to a rectangle.
It can adjust the corners of the board to a rectangle.
It's easier to adjust the seams or the front waves.
It can be made into a v-shaped board.
We can use the tool to edit the board.
Select this URL.
You can see it here.
In English, we will translate it into Chinese later.
Change it to a rectangle.
Here we can set the length of the rectangle.
And its direction.
Click OK when it's done.
This is the rectangle I just set.
The length is 50.
Next, we can make an improvement.
Yes, we can make an improvement when we create an inner line.
We can choose.
This inner line is a bit monotonous.
The inner line is sharp.
Before, when we created it,
we could only create it on one side.
Now we can choose this one on both sides.
Now we can create it on both sides at the same time.
Now we don't need to do this operation twice.
We can complete it at once.
Now we can extend the inner line.
Now we go to the outside of the board.
You can see that the inner line is extended directly to the outside of the board.
There is another one called the inner line.
The inner line is extended directly to the inside of the board.
It is not placed on the outside of the board.
Next, we can make an improvement on the path.
First, we select this point and then we make it an increase.
We have newly added a new adjustment path in the improvement path.
The adjustment path of the on and off keys.
If we choose this adjustment path,
and then click confirm,
this one,
confirm the adjustment path,
we click confirm.
After clicking confirm,
by adjusting or deleting the point of the curve.
Yes, our speed is indeed increasing.
I'm really sorry today.
Please bear with me for a while.
We're done with this path.
The next step is to improve the cutout.
Previously, we could add a cutout directly on the straight line.
Now we can also add a cutout on the straight line.
We can add a cutout anywhere.
We can also lock the cutout.
We can also lock the direction and distance of the cutout.
Let's change the distance to 50.
Let's start from the top.
The distance from the top to the straight line is 50.
Let's see.
When I change the length of this line,
you can see the position of my blade.
If the position of the straight line is 50,
it will not change.
We can lock the length of this line.
We just locked one end.
If you need to lock it in the middle,
you can add a cutout on the other side.
Then we can lock it.
The next step is to improve the cutout on the straight line.
Let's choose any point.
We can align all the numbers to this point.
Let's make an alignment.
Align it to the x-axis or the y-axis.
Or align it to that point.
This way, it's easier for us to see
what's different about each number.
We can do this for any point.
The next step is to measure the point.
When we use POM to measure the point
on the board with a square-shape,
it will measure the length of all the numbers one by one.
This way, we don't need to measure each number one by one.
The next step is to optimize the length of the board.
When we use a longer board,
we can use it for cross-boards.
Let's take a look.
We can use a cross-board to measure the length of the board.
In the process of measuring,
we can right-click on the board
and rotate it horizontally.
The next step is called a guide line.
It will take us to the point of the board.
When we create a guide line,
the guide line will automatically
take us to the point of the board.
This way, we don't need to manually align the boards.
The next step is called an extension board.
The guide lines can be moved simultaneously.
On a board with a guide line and a cross-board,
we can use an extension board tool
to extend the board.
The guide line will move along the board
and move into the position together.
Now, that's it.
Once the board has been modified,
we will no longer need to modify the position of the guide line.
Next, we have another new feature,
which is also the last feature I talked about,
which is auto-select.
Now, when we just released 6.0,
we can automatically select its top,
such as a shirt,
and now we can automatically select its pants.
All we need to do is to open the arranger,
and then arrange its layers
and the position of the panels for it.
Because our auto-select,
it is divided according to the position of the arranger.
Let me take a look.
I'll arrange it first.
After arranging it like this,
I'll click on this auto-select.
Please turn off the arranger.
First of all,
now there is an option
that allows you to select the type you need.
For safety,
you can select the pattern type.
Let's look at the direction.
Here, we only need to select the pants.
And then,
we can select the pattern type.
we need to select the pants.
And then,
click OK.
So,
the pants are automatically sewed.
this is the new feature that I will talk about.
And then,
next,
we welcome another teacher,
Evelyn,
the teacher who did the wedding live for you last time,
to talk about our new feature in the second half.
She was the first to introduce us from the very beginning.
And then,
we have some more materials.
We're going to see about the template.
First,
I will explain how to draw,
and then I will explain how to update it.
So,
if you want to see a sample of the template,
all you need to do is to click here and there.
You can just drag it and paste it.
Then,
if you open the template,
you can see the template.
So,
let me go to the details on what we have learned.
virtual models, and various modes.
The first part is our interface.
Let's take a look at our first new function,
which is the change UI.
As you all know, in Cloud,
all of our lines,
the external line, the internal line,
or the basic line,
all have their respective colors.
Let's come to the settings,
user self-definition.
In the user interface,
we can set the colors of our different lines.
Here I change it to green.
You can see that the external line of the board has changed.
At the same time,
I can also choose a rough display of our line.
You can also change the font size of the length of our line.
This makes it easier for everyone to see.
The next new function is to display the color of the hidden freezing and hardening.
You can see that there are many parts in our file that have been frozen and hardened.
We can come to our attribute editor,
come to our 3D window background.
On the right, there is a Hide All, Hide Show Color option.
We will use this part later.
It will be Han painting.
Don't worry.
We can hide the colors of the frozen and hardening,
or we can hide the colors of the partial adjustment that Ms. Molly showed.
Next, we will come to some updates on our materials.
First, let's look at the update content for the component.
The first new function of the add-on is to open the TRM file when there is no file.
You can see that before 6.1, if we do not open the file, there is no way to open the TRM format add-on file.
There is also no way to open the OBJ file as an add-on.
However, after 6.1, you can see that we can open the add-on separately.
The next update is about the display of the add-on in the scene bar.
I will now open a project file.
In 6.1, you can see that this project file is the same as the add-on.
There are multiple add-ons in this project file.
There are add-ons in the front and the back.
We can go to the object window and select the scene.
Under the 3D Simulate category, there is a Close Controller.
Here we can find the display of all the add-ons.
Accordingly, we can also click on different add-on names to see if they are displayed in the 3D window.
Next, we come to a new function about the conflict processing of add-ons.
When we select the front display, we add the add-on file in the 3D space center.
Place it in the appropriate position.
Adjust its position carefully.
After placing it, we can go to the property editor and find the conflict option.
Here we can also adjust the collision thickness.
In order to increase the speed of the simulation, I first reactivate the file that is not involved in the simulation.
Then we can start the simulation.
As you can see, in the case of the collision of the add-ons,
the add-on did not penetrate through the ring, but maintained its shape.
Here, if we use the glue tool to stick the add-on onto the clothing,
we can't open the conflict.
We need to pay attention to this.
The next new function is about selecting and moving multiple add-ons.
In 6.1, we can select multiple add-ons and OBJs at the same time.
Then we can select them.
We can move them in a general way.
The next part is about the updates related to the logic editor.
First, we can adjust the border and parallel of the logic repetition.
Let's open the logic editor.
After adding a material,
we can go to the repeat screen.
Here, we can see that we can set the border between the logic repetition,
an extra-y axis,
and its parallel.
We can do a faster and more accurate design like this.
The next new function is about storing the logic in layers.
Let's add some other materials first.
Let's do some design.
After adding other materials,
we can adjust its mixing mode.
After that,
click Save Images.
Save Images.
Here, I've selected the background.
Then select a storage path.
I've just created one.
As you can see,
all the saved images are in our computer.
It is also a PNG image with a transparent background.
In other words,
we can easily apply it in other CAD software.
This transparent path also exists.
After that,
let's take a look at the new function of opening the logic in PSAI in 6.1.
This is a new function of adding a third-party program connection.
Here, I use Photoshop as an example.
Click Open With.
Open it.
Then,
after choosing the program to be added,
in the computer,
in our system,
we can find the execution program that needs to be added to the application.
Then,
after completing it,
we can choose to open it.
We can add it to the cloud
and directly open the logic in our cloud.
Then,
we can make some modifications to it in Photoshop.
After the modification,
save it.
Cover and save.
Then,
when we return to the cloud page,
as long as we select the refresh pattern in the background,
we can see the modified logic effect.
At the same time,
we just use Photoshop as an example.
You can also add other software to make a connection.
In the user self-identification,
you can also add other different application programs.
Now,
we come to the new function of using the same color as the previous one.
First,
in order to demonstrate,
I remove the same material used in the previous one.
Delete the texture.
Then,
I assign a color to the previous fabric.
Come to the back,
select Use Same Color as Front.
Use the same color as the previous one.
Then,
you can see that the plant in the back
applies the same color as the previous one.
Next,
I open a new file.
We use this new file to demonstrate
a function update in the button function.
Our first new function
is to create a button between the start point and the end point.
In order to make it easier to see,
we switch the 2D and 3D window texture surface display mode
to the black and white surface.
Using our button,
we can change the color to black and white.
Then,
we use our button tool.
In the place where we need to add a button,
right-click,
there is a button window
that creates a button with the outline of the panel.
Select Distribute.
Then,
enter the distance.
This distance is the distance between the front and the back.
Next,
enter the starting point.
Then,
enter the end point.
We don't need to calculate the distance between the buttons.
We only need to enter the total number of buttons
in the repeated column.
Then,
our system will automatically calculate its distance
and generate an average distribution of button groups.
Next,
we will demonstrate the next function.
First,
we copy and paste the button to the symmetrical panel.
Then,
we remember our button.
we use the select button tool
to the familiar editor.
You can see that
we remember the position of the button.
In this column,
there is a drop-down menu.
Here,
we can enter the length of the button
based on the length set by the system.
We can enter the size of the button
based on the position of the button.
You can see the difference
after entering different sizes.
Next,
we will talk about the update of the virtual model.
In 6.1,
when we use the virtual model,
we use the virtual model measurement tool.
On our virtual model,
we can draw some measurements.
It can be the surface circumference measurement
or the basic length measurement.
After drawing,
I will give you a different example.
Next,
we will use the editing measurement tool.
So,
the model is a virtual model.
We can choose the duplicate to symmetric position
on the right side of the model.
It is the virtual model measurement tool
that generates symmetry.
We can match the symmetry
to the corresponding position
of the virtual model body
on the other side of the model body.
Isn't it more convenient
to draw the border line?
Next,
we will enter
some optimization of the different modes.
First of all, our first part is in our cherry blossom release mode.
In this mode, as Ms. Molly just talked about, not only when we generate the reference line, there is a copy on the board.
When we arrange the board in the cherry blossom release mode, we can also copy the board to the reference line.
Our next new function is to copy to the Reference Center.
To make it easier for everyone to see, I changed the pattern for the costume.
When I click on the 2D window,
I can see that there is a new center in the Reference Center.
When I select the Reference Center, I can see the reference line.
When I move the board, I find that the board has a copy function on the reference line.
The update in 6.1 is to increase the reference line.
This is a representation of the Reference Center.
In this way, when we arrange the board, we can copy the board to the Reference Center.
The next update is about the color blue.
As you can see,
we have added a lot of sticky panels to this costume.
They are in the sleeve, the back, and the front of the collar.
Including the waist of our jeans.
In the 6.1 version,
you can see that these panels are not only displayed on the different fabrics we applied,
but they are also displayed in an independent sticky panel.
This makes it easier for everyone to calculate the amount of sticky panels.
In 6.1, we also made some updates to the quick photo.
When we click on the save picture,
we can see that there is a display picture column in the pop-up window.
In this window,
we can choose whether we want to save the texture of the fabric in the final quick photo,
or the texture of the background.
If we want to display the texture in the background,
we can also use opacity to adjust its transparency.
In order not to display sensitive information,
we have done some mosaic processing here.
At the same time,
when we save,
in the previous version,
we can only save the quick photo of the JPG and PNG format.
But in 6.1,
we support saving the PDF format.
Let's save it.
Then open it and take a look.
This is the PDF format we saved.
The next part of the new function,
we come to the color mode.
In the color mode of 6.1,
we added color classification.
In the color bar,
we have the same color.
All the colors that appear in it,
and put them together at the top.
In the past,
when we changed multiple materials,
we had to press Shift
to select multiple objects
to change their colors at the same time.
But now,
we can directly select the color unit.
Click
the color unit in color classification
to quickly change the color of all the applied colors.
In the 6.1 version,
there is also a new function
that many viewers have been looking forward to,
which is the display and hiding of stickers.
We can add different stickers
during the production process.
And,
by adjusting the display and hiding of each sticker
in the color mode,
we can make different stickers
and apply different stickers.
You can take a look at it.
And,
please note that
the stickers that are hidden in our color
will not be displayed
in our Closet process.
If you want to hide them,
you can hide them in the color and hiding of stickers.
Now,
let's go to the fabric calculation mode.
Compared to the previous step 6,
there are only textiles.
In the 6.1 version,
we can add other textiles
other than textiles.
After we input
these valid values,
we can measure
the fabric by inputting the valid values.
In the 6th part,
in the Basic mode,
In Basic Parameters, you can add a texture image, a texture image, an illusion image, and a transparent image.
Here, I added a texture image and an illusion image.
This material has no illusion effect, so I won't add anything else.
In Reflection, you can add a rough surface, i.e. a high-gloss image, and a metal layer.
After you're done, click Save, and save it.
Next, let's apply the previously saved material.
As you can see, we now have a virtual material that includes physical properties and physical properties.
Now, let's go to the UV Editor mode.
In 6.1, not only can our clothing display the UV image, but also the name of the line can be saved in the UV image.
To save the name of the line in the UV image, you can select OBJ or Texture for the name of the line.
Let's take a look.
Under the name of the line in the OBJ format,
the UV mode will automatically generate a UV image of the name of the line in the OBJ format.
However, if we change the name of the line to Texture,
the name of the line in the Texture format will be displayed as a texture on the UV image of the clothing in the UV editor.
Will the texture image appear in the rendered image?
Oh, this...
If we're talking about the display of the UV image,
if the texture image is hidden,
then the hidden texture image will not appear in the rendered image.
Don't worry.
Now, let's come to the last new feature that we need to demonstrate today.
In the material list mode,
we have added a new function,
which is the display of the UV image and the name of the line in the material list.
This is to make it easier for you to calculate the cost in a more detailed way.
That's it for our demonstration.
We have some other new features that we haven't demonstrated yet.
For example, starting from 6.1,
we also support the SSO and AD FS platforms of the single machine.
The second point is,
in 6.1,
if we use the Wacom 3D pen,
our system can identify the pressure of the 3D pen
when using tools such as the grid pen brush.
The third point is the method of mixing the lines.
If you're interested,
you can find out about it yourself.
I won't go into too much detail here,
because this concept is relatively deep.
The last point is,
we're going to show you how to mix the lines.
In the new version of 6.1,
the maximum width of the line is 50mm.
That's it for the main functions.
If you have any questions,
you can ask them to me and Molly.
Let me see.
Let's see.
Molly,
come here.
I can see you.
Molly,
come here.
Okay.
Now,
let me take this diorama here,
so that we can see
that the tips can match the lines each other.
Okay.
It will have a different effect when you paste the picture
Let's let Molly come over here
Do you have any other questions?
I know today is a very tough day
I'm sure Molly and I didn't expect this
Can we change the color of the text in the text color?
You mean you want to change the text color in our software?
If you want it to be like this
This seems like a good idea
No, it's not
It's not good
The best way is to find a professional CAD software
It might be more convenient
We won't do it again like this
There will be a live broadcast later
But if you think this live broadcast is too short
You can go and watch our live broadcast
It's hard for everyone
I see that some of the audience have been following us since the beginning
When they were stuck
All the way to the end
Thank you all
Today it seems like
It's a bit of a problem to post chats like this
Yes
We can't even post it ourselves
Xiao Xi Jun is about to cry
Yes, we haven't posted it yet
Yes
Let's see if there are any more questions
We can post chats to these people
You can ask questions
There are indeed some questions in the chats today
Yes
In the PS interface
What?
What does it say?
What's wrong?
You guys
Didn't punch each other
Yes
You lost a few words
What happened when you found the 3D interface?
It's so awkward
It's changed
I don't know
Why?
Come on
See
You
It's not changed
You did it with transparency in the PS interface
Or
Or something
If you can't explain it
You can post it later
At the back of our wechat public expression
We can take a look
Yes
We can ask
Yes and then
That should be fine
Can you confirm if your RGB color channel is 8-way?
Let's see
Is there anything else you're interested in about new features?
What's your next live stream about?
I think it's also a Thursday
I hope it won't be so hard
It's definitely fine
I'm looking forward to the details behind you
I'm stressed
Me too
If you want to see more live streams, you can post them in the comments
That's right
If there are no more questions, we'll end the live stream today
We'll end the live stream
I know
We'll see you next time
Bye-bye
I hope you all have a good weekend
That's right
Bye-bye
How do you change the Xuer window to the original one?
You mean the Xuer window tool bar, right?
Yes
We can't change the tool bar right now
We'll add a tool bar to the Xuer window tool bar later
You can look forward to the optimized version of the Xuer window tool bar
Next, we'll add a small update
Yes, we'll add a small update
That's right
Now it's all vertical
Yes, vertical
That's right
We've asked the developer for advice
Please be patient and wait for it
Bye-bye
It's the end of June 12th
I hope you all have a happy June 12th
I hope you all have a happy weekend
Bye-bye
See you
Take control
Bye-bye
Nice day
What a day
Yes, it was nice
I finished my homework